Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958 RL.00655
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Sylvania, 1955-1956; 48
  - Other Programming, 1955-1956; 119
    - Buffalo Christian Show, 1955 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Syracuse show, 1956 May 3 (Film-reel 1011)
- Textron, 1945-1949; 49
  - Textron Theatre, 1945 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 281)
  - Textron Theatre, 1945 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 283)
  - Textron Theatre--Helen Hayes, 1946 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 343)
  - Textron Theatre--The Hartmans, 1949 Feb.-May (Film-reel 718)
  - This is Helen Hayes, 1945 Feb.-July (Film-reel 281)
- The Circle Dramatic Scripts, 1935-1939; 50
  - Accent on Youth (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Feb.20 (Film-reel 48)
  - Bad Man (Chase & Sanborn), 1937 Aug. 29 (Film-reel 48)
  - Biography (Shell), 1936 Sept. 5 (Film-reel 48)
  - Call It a Day (Shell), 1936 June 20 (Film-reel 48)
  - Candlelight (Chase & Sanborn), 1937 June 6 (Film-reel 48)
  - Coquette (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Nov. 6 (Film-reel 48)
  - Cyrano de Bergerac (Shell), 1935 May 25 (Film-reel 48)
  - Death Takes a Holiday (Kellogg/Circle), 1939 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 48)
  - Green Goddess (Shell), 1935 Aug. 31 (Film-reel 48)
  - Holiday (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 48)
  - Is Zat So? (Shell), 1935 Sept. 21 (Film-reel 48)
  - June Moon (Shell), 1936 May 2 (Film-reel 48)
  - Just Suppose (Shell), 1935 Aug. 31 (Film-reel 48)
  - Let Us Be Gay (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Sept. 25 (Film-reel 48)
  - Monkey's Paw (Kellogg/Circle), 1939 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 48)
  - Mrs. Moonlight (Shell), 1936 Apr. 18 (Film-reel 48)
  - Napoleon's Barber (Shell), 1935 Dec. 14 (Film-reel 48)
  - Old Lady Shows Her Medals (Chase & Sanborn), 1935 June 20 (Film-reel 48)
  - Rip Van Winkle (Shell), 1935 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 48)
  - Romantic Young Lady (Chase & Sanborn), 1937 June 27 (Film-reel 48)
  - The Copperhead (Shell), 1935 Aug. 17 (Film-reel 48)
  - The Curtain Rises (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Oct. 16 (Film-reel 48)
  - The Last Mile (Shell), 1935 Oct. 26 (Film-reel 48)
  - The Londonderry Air (Chase & Sanborn), 1937 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 48)
  - There's Always Juliet (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Oct. 30 (Film-reel 48)
  - You and I (Chase & Sanborn), 1938 Aug. 14 (Film-reel 48)
- U.S. Industrial Alcohol (Pyro), 1931-1933; 51
  - Audition script, 1933 (Film-reel 32)
  - Boston, 1932 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 243)
  - Commercial, 1931 (Film-reel 32)
  - WEAF, 1932 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 243)
- U.S. Playing Card Co., 1940-1941; 52
  - Commercials, 1941 Nov.-1942 Jan. (Film-reel 170)
  - Commercials, 1940 Nov. (Film-reel 179)
  - Scripts and commercials, 1941 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 170)
- Union Central Life Insurance Co.--Roses and Drums, 1932-1935; 53
  - 1932 May-Aug. (Film-reel 125)
  - 1932 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 126)
    Oct. 9-Dec. 4, 1932 no scripts--show broadcast from Chicago
  - 1933 Jan.-1934 Feb. (Film-reel 126)
  - 1934 Feb.-Dec. (Film-reel 127)
    off air during summer
  - 1935 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 130)
  - 1935 Aug.-1936 Mar. (Film-reel 131)
- United Churches Canvass, 1935-1948; 54
  - One Man's Family, 1935-1948; 120
    - History in Words and Pictures, 1935 (Film-reel 417)
    - 1948 Jan.-May (Film-reel 417)
    - 1948 June-Aug. (Film-reel 417)
    - 1948 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 418)
  - Other Programming, 1937-1948; 121
    - Commercials, 1948 (Film-reel 418)
    - Edgar Bergen Show, 1948 Jan.-May; Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 418)
      No broadcast Apr. 11; Dec. 19 broadcast missing
    - Fleischmann's Yeast for Bread, 1938 June 29 (Film-reel 418)
    - Royal Baking Powder, 1937 June 29 (Film-reel 418)
    - Royal Desserts, 1937 July 1 (Film-reel 418)
    - Royal Pudding, Desserts--Robert Shaw Chorale, 1948 June-Sept. (Film-reel 418)
    - U.S. Marine Corps/Major Gen. Alexander Archer Vandergrift, 1943 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 201)
- United Nations Information Bureau, 1943; 55
  - Eight Legal Governments of Invaded Europe: What They Are Doing To Defeat Hitler and Establish Peace, 1943 (Film-reel 201)
  - Norway, 1943 (Film-reel 201)
  - Yugoslavia, 1943 (Film-reel 201)
- Universal Pictures, 1937-1943; 56
  - Commercials, 1942 Dec. 21-22 (Film-reel 262)
  - Flesh and Fantasy--Commercials, 1943 Oct. (Film-reel 201)
  - Hellzapoppin--Commercials, 1941 Dec.-1942 Jan. (Film-reel 171)
  - 1937 (Film-reel 33)
- W.F. Young, Inc. (Absorbine Jr.), 1938-1946; 57
  - Commercials, 1938 June 3 (Film-reel 150)
  - Happy Endings (Sample radio script by John A. Carter), 1946 Jan. 14 (Film-reel 305)
  - Spot announcements, 1943 Mar.-June (Film-reel 201)
  - True Or False program, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1941 July-Sept. (Film-reel 182)
- Ward Baking Co., 1941-1949; 58
  - Commercials, 1945-1948; 122
    - H-E-P recorded spots, 1946 Dec.-1947 Jan. (Film-reel 370)
    - KQV Pittsburg, Pa., 1948 Jan.-June (Film-reel 370)
    - KSO St. Louis, Mo., 1948 Jan.-July (Film-reel 370)
    - WAGE Syracuse, N.Y., 1947 July-1948 July (Film-reel 370)
    - WALT music program, 1948 June-July (Film-reel 371)
    - WAPI Birmingham, Ala., 1946-1948 July (Film-reel 369)
    - WBAL Baltimore, Md., 1946 Nov.-1948 July (Film-reel 372)
    - WCAO Baltimore, Md., 1948 Jan.-June (Film-reel 371)
    - WCAO Baltimore, Md., 1948 July (Film-reel 372)
    - WCBS New York, N.Y., 1947 Apr.-1948 July (Film-reel 372)
      The Missus Goes A-Shopping
    - WDEV Waterbury, Vt., 1946-1948 July (Film-reel 371)
      Tip Top Musical Almanac
    - WEAN Providence, R.I., 1948 Jan.-July (Film-reel 372)
      Tello-Test
    - WEEI Boston, Mass., 1948 Feb.-July (Film-reel 372)
      Breakfast in Boston
    - WEEI Boston, Mass., 1948 Jan.-July (Film-reel 372)
      Top 'o the Morning
    - WEEI Boston, Mass., 1947 July-1948 Mar. (Film-reel 372)
    - WFBR Baltimore, Md., 1947 June-1948 July (Film-reel 372)
    - WFLA Tampa, Fla., 1947 June-1948 July (Film-reel 372)
    - WGES Chicago, Ill., 1946-1947 July (Film-reel 372)
      Polish Dinner Bell
    - WGN Chicago, Ill., 1947 June-1948 July (Film-reel 372)
      Musical Clock, Record, Reveille
    - WHFC The Bohemian Hour, 1948 Spring (Film-reel 370)
    - WHK Cleveland, Oh., 1948 Jan.-July (Film-reel 370)
    - WHKC Columbus, Oh., 1947 May-1948 July (Film-reel 372)
      15 minute news
    - WJAX Jacksonville, Fla., 1946 Feb.-1948 July (Film-reel 370)
    - WJAX Jacksonville, Fla., 1946-1948 Mar. (Film-reel 371)
      Tip Top Tunes new programming
    - WLEU Erie, Pa., 1948 Jan.-May (Film-reel 370)
    - WLEU Erie, Pa., 1947-1948 (Film-reel 371)
      Includes spots for Florida announcement, Aunt Hannah's Kiddie Show
    - WNAC Boston, Mass., 1948 Mar.-July (Film-reel 370)
    - WNEW New York, N.Y., 1948 Jan.-July (Film-reel 370)
    - WNLC New London, Conn., 1946-1948 July (Film-reel 370)
    - WPDQ Jacksonville, Fla., 1946 Oct.-1947 Jan. (Film-reel 369)
    - WPDQ Jacksonville, Fla., 1947 Feb.-1948 July (Film-reel 370)
    - WSBC Chicago, Ill., 1945 Dec.-1948 July (Film-reel 370)
    - WSBT South Bend, Ind., 1946-1948 July (Film-reel 370)
    - WSGN Birmingham, Ala., 1948 Jan.-July (Film-reel 370)
    - WSUN, 1947 July-1948 July (Film-reel 370)
    - WWNY Watertown, N.Y., 1945 Nov.-1948 July (Film-reel 370)
    - WXYZ Detroit, Mich., 1948 Jan.-July (Film-reel 370)
  - Dick Tracy, 1944-1945; 123
    - KQV, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - KXOK, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WAGE, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WAGE, 1945 May-Aug. (Film-reel 267)
    - WCOL, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WENR, 1944 Apr.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WENR, 1945 May-Aug. (Film-reel 267)
    - WFIL, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WFIL, 1945 May (Film-reel 267)
    - WFMJ, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 267)
    - WFMJ, 1945 May (Film-reel 267)
    - WHDH, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WHOT, 1944 Oct.-1945 Mar. (Film-reel 266)
    - WHOT, 1945 Apr.-May (Film-reel 267)
    - WICI, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WJHP, 1944 Oct.-1945 May (Film-reel 267)
    - WJW, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 267)
    - WJZ, 1944 Apr.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WKIP, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WLEU, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WLEU, 1945 May-Aug. (Film-reel 267)
    - WNAB, 1944 May-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WNBC, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WORC, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WORC, 1945 May-Aug. (Film-reel 267)
    - WSGN, 1945 Feb.-May (Film-reel 267)
    - WSGN, 1945 May-July (Film-reel 267)
    - WTRY, 1944 Oct.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WTRY, 1945 May-Aug. (Film-reel 267)
    - WWVA, 1944 Sept.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
    - WXYZ, 1944 Oct.-1945 May (Film-reel 266)
  - Other Programming, 1941-1949; 124
    - Aunt Hannah's Bread commercials, 1948 (Film-reel 421)
    - Aunt Hannah's Bread sots, 1945 Jan. (Film-reel 311)
    - Aunt Hannah's Enriched Bread, 1943 Apr.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 265)
    - Aunt Hannah's Kiddie Show, 1948 Jan.-1949 Apr. (Film-reel 717)
    - Bread and cake spot announcements, 1948 Feb.-July; 1948 Jan. (Film-reel 421)
    - Commercials, 1941 Sept.-1942 Sept. (Film-reel 175)
    - Judy & Jane, 1943 Jan.-July (Film-reel 265)
    - Marjorie Mills, N.E. Network, 1942 Dec.-1943 Feb. (Film-reel 245)
    - Participation spots, 1948 Jan.-July (Film-reel 422)
    - Phil Cook Show comics audition, 1941 (Film-reel 175)
    - Sales meeting (not to be broadcast), 1945 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 281)
    - Spot announcements, 1943 June 21 (Film-reel 207)
    - Spot announcements, 1943-1944 (Film-reel 265)
    - Spot announcements, 1946 (Film-reel 312)
    - Spot announcements, 1948 Jan.-July (Film-reel 422)
    - Various stations, 1943-1944 (Film-reel 265)
    - Various stations, 1943-1944 (Film-reel 266)
  - Spot announcements, 1943-1946; 125
    - KDKA, 10 minute, 1945 Jan.-June (Film-reel 270)
    - KMOX, 1943 June-Sept. (Film-reel 268)
    - KMOX, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 270)
    - KMOX, WJAX, 1943 Sept.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 268)
    - KSD, 15 minute, 1943 June-1944 May (Film-reel 269)
    - WABC, 15 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 June (Film-reel 269)
    - WAPI, 15 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 269)
    - WAPI, 15 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WBBM, 1944 May-Dec. (Film-reel 268)
    - WBBM, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 270)
    - WBNS, 1943 May-1944 May (Film-reel 267)
    - WBNS, 15 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 July (Film-reel 269)
    - WCAO, 5 minute, 1946 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 270)
    - WCBM, 15 minute, 1943 Oct.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 269)
    - WCBM, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 270)
    - WDEV, 1945 July-Dec. (Film-reel 270)
    - WFBR, 1943 Dec.-1944 Feb. (Film-reel 268)
    - WFBR, 15 minute, 1944 Feb.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 269)
    - WFBR, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-1946 May (Film-reel 270)
    - WFBR, 5 minute, 1944 Jan.-Dec. (Film-reel 268)
    - WFBR, 5 minute, 1945 Jan.-1946 May (Film-reel 270)
    - WFMJ, 5 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 268)
    - WFMJ, 5 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WGES, 1944 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 267)
      Polish Dinner Bell, Mrs. Emily Rewicx
    - WGES, 15 minute, 1944 Jan.-May (Film-reel 268)
    - WGES, 15 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WGN, 15 minute, 1944 Apr.-Oct. (Film-reel 269)
    - WHKC, 15 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WHKC, 30 minute, 1944 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 269)
    - WIBG, 15 minute, 1945 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 270)
    - WITH, 1943 May-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 267)
    - WITH, 15 minute, 1945 jan.-1946 Jan. (Film-reel 270)
    - WJAX, 15 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WJR, 10 minute, 1943 Oct.-1944 July (Film-reel 268)
    - WJW, 15 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 269)
    - WJW, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-June (Film-reel 270)
    - WKBN, 5 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Jan. (Film-reel 267)
    - WKBN, 5 minute, 1944 Jan.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 268)
    - WKBN, 5 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WMBR, 10 minute, 1945 Jan.-June (Film-reel 270)
    - WMBR, 15 minute, 1944 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 269)
    - WNAC, 5 minute, 1944 Feb.-Dec. (Film-reel 267)
    - WNAC, 5 minute, 1945 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 269)
    - WNLC, 5 minute, 1944 Feb.-Dec. (Film-reel 267)
    - WNLC, 5 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WOR, 15 minute, 1943 Sept.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 268)
    - WOR, 15 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WSBC, 1944 (Film-reel 267)
    - WSBC, 15 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WSBT, 1943 Oct.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 267)
    - WSBT, 15 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WWJ, 15 minute, 1944 Dec.-1945 Feb. (Film-reel 269)
    - WWJ, 15 minute, 1944 Feb.-1945 June (Film-reel 270)
      Dates missing
    - WWNY, 5 minute, 1943 Dec.-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 267)
    - WWNY, 5 minute, 1945 (Film-reel 270)
    - WWSW, Aunt Hannah, 1945 Jan.-Oct. (Film-reel 270)
    - WXYZ, 1943 May-1944 Dec. (Film-reel 267)
    - WXYZ, 15 minute, 1945 Jan.-July (Film-reel 270)
    - 1943 May-Sept. (Film-reel 268)
    - 1943 (Film-reel 270)
  - Tennessee Jed, 1945-1947; 126
    - Auditions, 1946 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 313)
    - 1945 (Film-reel 281)
      Through episode 17
    - 1945 (Film-reel 282)
      Episodes 18-on; missing episodes 31-34
    - 1946 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 312)
    - 1946 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 313)
      Missing Aug. 20; no broadcast Aug. 21-22
    - 1947 Jan.-May (Film-reel 368)
    - 1947 May-Nov. (Film-reel 369)
  - Tip Top Bread, 1942-1948; 127
    - Audition, spot announcements, 1943 June 21 (Film-reel 206)
    - Commercials--Enriched Tip Top Bread, Judy and Jane, 1943 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 206)
    - Commercials--Enriched Tip Top Bread, Judy and Jane, 1943 Mar.-July (Film-reel 207)
    - Commercials--Enriched Tip Top Bread, Terry and the Pirates, 1942 Apr.-Sept. (Film-reel 206)
    - Jingles, Advox commercials, 1948 Dec. 14 (Film-reel 421)
    - Recorded spots, 1947 Jan.1948 Jan. (Film-reel 421)
    - Spot announcements, 1943 July 16 (Film-reel 206)
    - Spot announcements, 1943 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 244)
    - Spot announcements, 1943 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 245)
- William Wrigley Jr., 1939-1943; 59
  - Doublemint Gum, 1939-1942; 128
    - Commercials, 1939 Dec.-1942 Apr. (Film-reel 169)
  - Gene Autry Show, 1941-1943; 129
    - Melody Ranch, 1942 Apr.-Dec. (Film-reel 170)
    - 1941 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 207)
    - 1941 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 208)
    - 1943 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 208)